Similar to the end of the last lesson,
与上节课类似
we'll be using Scikit-learn to performer our model diagnostics.
我们将要使用机器学习库 Scikit-learn 进行模型诊断
We will be using the admittance data from the previous quiz you did in Python.
使用之前你在 Python 中完成上次测验的导入数据
In the next concept,
在接下来的页面中
you'll perform these operations to make sure you can do this on your own.
你要完成这些操作 确保独立完成
Here, you can see we've loaded our libraries and the necessary data set.
这里你可以看到我们已经加载库和必要的数据集
So, here's the admissions data set here,
这是入学的数据集
and then you'll see that our metrics that we're using are any of these.
然后你会看到我们使用过的衡量标准
And then we have logistic regression as our model,
然后使用逻辑回归作为模型
that I imported from Scikit-learn,
我导入了 Scikit-learn
and we imported the train test split,
导入训练 测试和拆分
like you did at the end of the last lesson.
正如你上节课最后所做的
First, let's split our data set into training and testing data.
首先我们拆分数据集 训练和测试数据
And I also want to just pull off the X and Y components to do this.
同时我也希望像这样完成 X 和 Y 部分
We want Y to be whether or not they're admitted,
Y 表示是否入学
and we're going to have X just be the other parts.
X 表示其余部分
So, we can create prestige as a dummy variable here.
所以我们这里创建声望 (prestige) 作为虚拟变量
So, basically you can see I added four levels,
这样你可以看到我增加了 4 个等级
and then I'm passing the prestige portion and basically with the one through four,
传递了声望 (prestige) 部分 从 4 个中挑选 1 个
will get coded as their own columns here,
进行编码 作为单独一列
and then I'll leave one of those columns out just
然后我删除其中一列
so we have a four ring matrix, through one and two.
然后通过 1 和 2 得到一个四环矩阵
And here you can specify the random state so
这里你可以指定随机状态
that you get the same results every time you run this,
每次运行时都可以得到相同结果
and you'll see we'll get these four parts back.
可以看到我们得到了 4 部分
Now, we want to perform our operations on the training set.
现在我们要对训练集完成操作
Similar to the last lesson,
与上节课类似
you might decide to transform your data in lots of ways to predict the response better.
你可以通过各种方式改变数据 更好地预测反应变量
However, the purpose of this video is simply to look
不过 这个视频的目的只是
at the matrix available for us in Scikit-learn.
要观察 Scikit-learn 中可以得到的矩阵
Let's go and fit a model to our training data,
我们来拟合模型和训练的数据
and then we'll see how well it performs on the test data.
然后观察它是否较好地完成测试数据
So the first step to fitting our model,
所以第一步是拟合模型
is to instantiate our model.
就是要用具体例证说明模型
Here, I'm going to just specify using the default parameters.
这里我指定使用默认参数
If we actually go in and look,
如果我们深入了解
you'll see that there are a whole bunch of things that they could specify,
你会发现它们可以指定各种内容
and we want to just use the default for all of these in our particular case.
我们只想使用特殊案例中的默认值
However, there are ways that you can make
不过 你可以采取多种方式
sure that you choose the best one of each of these things.
选择最适合的内容
And then, we want to fit this model using the training data,
然后我们要使用训练数据拟合模型
so you specify X train.
所以你指定 X 训练
Let's see, if we look at the fit.
我们来看一下这个拟合
It asks for the X first and then the Y.
首先请求 X 其次是 Y
So, X train and then Y train.
所以先训练 X 然后训练 Y
So, we'll fit the model,
我们拟合模型
and then we want to predict.
然后进行预测
So, we're going to get Y, protocol Y preds.
接着我们拟定 Y preds
So we're going to predict on
我们对测试数据进行预测
the test data and we're going to use the X test data to do that.
然后使用 X 测试数据完成预测
And then basically, we could use any one of
基本来说 我们可以使用任一矩阵
these matrix to see how well our model is performing.
观察模型是否较好地完成任务
So if you look at things like this,
如果你看到这样的内容
the precision score or the recall score,
精确度分数和召回率分数
you'll see the first argument they take is the true response value,
你会发现得到的第一个参数值是正确的响应值
and the second value they take is the predicted value.
第二个参数值是预测值
And then you can get back, so in this case,
然后回到这里 在这种情况下
you'll get back the precision value for
你得到 Y 正确性的精确值
how the Y true and Y predicted compare to one another,
以及预测 Y 与其他值的对比
using exactly what Sebastian showed in those earlier videos.
利用 Sebastian 在之前视频中展示的内容
So, we could do things like get the precision score, get the recall score,
所以我们得到精确率分数 召回率分数
get the accuracy score,
准确率分数
and we can also get the confusion matrix.
也得到混淆矩阵
Accuracy, and finally, let's just get a confusion matrix.
准确率 最终我们得到了混淆矩阵
Cool.
非常棒
So, here you can see we have a precision of approximately 67 percent,
这里你可以看到精确分数约为 67%
our recall is about 12.5 percent, so not great there.
召回率约为 12.5% 并不算大
Our accuracy is around 63 percent,
准确度约为 63%
and then the confusion matrix,
然后是混淆矩阵
this 23 here says, of the zeros,
这里是 23 个 0
you predicted 23 of them to actually be zeros.
你预测了其中 23 个实际上是 0
And then this one down here says,
下面这个说明
of the ones you predicted,
在预测的这些中
two of them to actually be ones,
其中两个是 1
and then basically, this is prediction down this part,
下面这部分是预测
and this is truth up here.
上面这里是实际情况
Pretty sure that's true. We can verify.
可以确定这是正确的 我们可以进行验证
So, the predicted is down this axis,
所以预测位于这个轴的下方
and the actual is up here.
实际情况位于上方
So, here the predicted is zero,
这里预测为 0 1
one, and then the truth is zero, one.
实际也是 0 1
So these are truly zeros,
所以这些是正确的 0
and appear the 23 are the zeros that we actually predicted to be zeros.
这 23 个是我们预测为 0 实际上也是 0
These are zeros that we predicted to be ones,
这些是我们预测为 1 实际上是 0
these are ones that we predicted to be zeros,
这些是我们预测为 0 实际上是 1
and these are ones that we predicted to be ones.
这些是我们预测为 1 实际上是 1
Great. So with this,
非常棒 掌握这些内容
you're ready to take on the next part yourself.
你可以学习下一部分了